upsee.nic.in 2013-07-24

# Thanks for visiting website of Uttar Pradesh State Entrance Examination 2012 (UPSEE-2012), and reviewing our privacy policy. We collect no personal contact information, like telephone numbers or addresses , when you visit our website. If you choose to provide that information to us, it is only used to fulfill your request for information. We do collect some technical information when you visit to make your visit seamless. The section below explains how we handle and collect technical information when you visit our website. Information collected and stored automatically When you browse, read pages, or download information on this website, we automatically gather and store certain technical information about your visit. This information never identifies who you are. The information we collect and store about your visit is listed below: The Internet domain of your service provider vider (e.g. mtnl.net.in) and IP address (an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you’re surfing the web) from which you access our website.

                                         PRIVACY POLICIES
Thanks for visiting website of Uttar Pradesh State Entrance Examination 2012 (UPSEE-
2012), and reviewing our privacy policy.
We collect no personal contact information, like telephone numbers or addresses , when you
visit our website. If you choose to provide that information to us, it is only used to fulfill your
request for information.
We do collect some technical information when you visit to make your visit seamless. The
section below explains how we handle and collect technical information when you visit our
website.
Information collected and stored automatically When you browse, read pages, or download
information on this website, we automatically gather and store certain technical information
about your visit. This information never identifies who you are. The information we collect
and store about your visit is listed below:
The Internet domain of your service provider vider (e.g. mtnl.net.in) and IP address (an IP
address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you’re surfing
the web) from which you access our website.
    •   The type of browser (such as Firefox, Netscape, or Internet Explorer) and operating
        system (Windows, Linux) used to access our site .
    •   The date and time you accessed our site.
    •   The pages/URLs you have visited and
    •   If you reached this website from another website, the address of that referring
        website.
This information is only used to help us make the site more useful for you. With this data, we
learn about the number of visitors to our site and the types of technology our visitors use. We
never track or record information about individuals and their visits.
Cookies
When you visit some websites, they may download small pieces of software on your
computer/browsing device known as cookies. Some cookies collect personal information to
recognise your computer in the future. We only use non-persistent cookies or “per- session
cookies”.
Per-session cookies serve technical purposes, like providing seamless navigation through this
website. These cookies do not collect personal information on users and they are deleted as
soon as you leave our website. The cookies do not permanently record data and they are not
stored on your computer’s hard drive. The cookies are stored in memory and are only
available during an active browser session. Again, once you close your browser, the cookie
disappears.
If you send us personal information
We do not collect personal information for any purpose other than to respond to you (for
example, to respond to your questions or provide subscriptions you have chosen). If you
choose to provide us with personal information— like filling out a Contact Us form, with an
e-mail address or postal address, and submitting it to us through the website—we use that

information to respond to your message, and to help you get the information you’ve
requested. We only share the information you give us with another Government agency if
your question relates to that agency, or as otherwise required by law.
Our website never collects information or creates individual profiles for commercial
marketing. While you must provide an e-mail address for a localised response to any
incoming questions or comments to us, we recommend that you do NOT include any other
personal information.
Site Security
For site security purposes and to ensure that this service vice remains available to all users,
this Government computer system employs commercial software programs to monitor
network traffic to identify unauthorised attempts to upload or change information, or
otherwise cause damage.
    •   Except for authorised law enforcement investigations, no other attempts are made to
        identify individual users or their usage habits. Raw data logs are used for no other
        purposes and are scheduled for regular deletion.
    •   Unauthorised attempts to upload information or change information on this service
        are strictly prohibited and may be punishable under the Indian IT Act.
